

Ashwini Burkule

Full Stack Developer

Full Stack Developer with 2.8 years of experience in designing, developing, and managing complex sites and internal frameworks. Specialize in React JS, React-redux and responsive design. Have good experience in building websites and demo products for TCS that drive business growth.

ashwiniburkule333@gmail.com

7350310931

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant System Engineer TCS

12/2016 - Present

1.Vodafone Project Full Stack Developer

01/2017 - 06/2017

CPOS (Centralized Point Of Sales) is application used across 23 circles PAN India for Vodafone customer acquisitions. It mainly handle CRS (Customer Registration System), Number and Project Management.

Tasks

- Had a walk through the Solution document for each change request and prepare logic to get Client Requirement.
- Develop code, UI changes, Scheduler changes as per change request of client within time and mainly work in CRS part of Project.
- Frameworks: Struts framework
- Language: Java, HTML, CSS, SQL

2.IT IS-Arch & Design CoE Full Stack Developer

07/2017 - Present

It is internal project of TCS.It is product base project of making demo products like DevOps Manager,Infra Manager.

Tasks

- Handling the product enhancement as per requirement.
- Also develop new product as per the market demand.
- Develop code , UI development , Scheduler changes as per change future growth in IT within time.
- Frameworks: Spring-boot framework
- Language: React-js,React-Redux,Javascript,hmtl,css,bootstrap,java,spring-boot

SKILLS

CSS3

React JS React-Redux Javascript HTML5

Java

Tools: Eclipse, Putty, sublime, svn, visual studio code.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Bootstrap

Vodafone Project (01/2017 - 06/2017)

IT IS-Arch & Design CoE (07/2017 – Present)

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Spring-boot

SOL

Marathi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Road trips

Music

EDUCATION

BE

Amravati University